=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 16=
Zhangzhu.
Ms. Lin.
Help me book a nearby French restaurant.
7 PM tonight, a table for two.
Okay.
Anything else?
Who am I going with, right?
With He Han.
I thought so.
Mr. He Han likes French food.
You have really taken your idol-chasing
to a very detailed level.
If you are a true fan,
you have to know
everything from head to toe.
Only then does it count.
What kind of fan is that?
You are just being ridiculous.
There is something
I think I have found a lead.
Whose problem is it?
It's Fragile.
Among the new authors I referred to her,
the first five
had contact
with Zhao Lanxin's company.
So, how do we handle her?
Let's wait and see.
Wait for what?
For tonight's
French restaurant reservation,
have Fragile make it.
Why?
She knows the manager there.
Got it.
Welcome.
Sir, would you like to
see what flowers we have?
Roses.
What color would you like?
Red.
How many would you like?
The more, the better.
I want the kind
where people see me
and know I am deeply in love.
Make it as over the top as possible.
Alright, got it.
Sir, you are really
straightforward and generous.
Would you like to add a card?
No need for a card.
Just give me an invoice.
Next time, we will go eat
at that noodle place I told you about.
Mr. He, waiting for our boss?
Is she off work yet?
Ms. Lin just finished
a meeting with the publicity team.
She will be down soon.
Okay.
We will head out first.
Bye.
We are leaving first, Mr. He.
These flowers look great.
They are for you.
Isn't this too much?
That is how I show sincerity.
You should not have spent so much.
I got you an invoice.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Mr. He Han took Ms. Lin out for dinner.
Our company
is going to be sold to Dingqi Platform.
You know that, right?
Mr. Fan will become our boss's boss.
I am just reminding
you to be more careful.
You are always
following Ms. Lin around,
back and forth, everywhere.
In the future, when you see Mr. Fan,
find chances to show yourself.
Plan ahead.
Okay.
Thank you, Fragile.
Please look out for me.
It is nothing. I am leaving.
You picked a good spot.
People can see us clearly from outside.
How long do you plan to sit here?
I need to go back
early today to call Gu Yan.
He is not in a good state.
At least three hours.
If we are putting on a show,
we have to go all the way.
But we cannot possibly talk that long.
Why not?
I have plenty to share with you.
Even three hours feels short to me.
Ms. Lin.
Mr. He.
New boyfriend?
He has always been this one.
They are seriously dating.
They probably think the same about us.
Here, have some cod.
Open your mouth.
Thanks.
You know I hate carrots.
I came here to help you.
Even if there is no return,
you still treat me like this.
How do you know there is no return?
What did you give me in return?
You're too proactive.
Won't it look too deliberate?
You should sit a bit closer to me now.
Otherwise, it will not look real.
This is exactly why
I came to see you today.
Flip to the back.
There are photos of
the nursing home where he lives
and his daily routine.
You have been there?
You should go take a look, too.
Isn't this good enough?
The caregiver said
he often loses his temper
and argues with people.
So now, some public entertainment places
don't allow him in anymore.
That is normal.
Has he not always been like that?
Nothing pleases him.
He is unhappy wherever he goes.
Honestly, he should not
be in a nursing home.
He should be in prison.
His health is not good.
Liver cancer.
When he came to see you that time,
he had probably already been diagnosed.
He refuses treatment.
He only took some painkillers.
The caregiver tried to get
him to quit smoking and drinking,
but it did not work.
Of course, it did not work.
No one can persuade him.
He will drink until the day he dies.
I told him to come back
to Shanghai for treatment.
Cancer is not
necessarily untreatable now.
At the very least, it could improve
his quality of life.
But seeing him like this,
if no one looks after him,
he won't have much time left.
That is good news.
We should celebrate.
One less disaster in this world.
Even if he changes...
I know what you are going to say.
You are going to say no matter what,
he is still my father.
Without him, there would be no me.
I know.
You have said that to me for ten years.
So you think
just because he is sick and dying,
I should forgive him?
Why?
When he put me
through all that back then,
he should have thought about today.
Not everyone in this world
deserves to be a father.
You don't need to
worry about him anymore.
And you don't need
to go see him anymore.
He is not worth it.
Do you know,
when you said that just now,
you sounded exactly like your father.
He has already bought his burial plot.
He sent me the contract.
He chose the cheapest one.
He said he knows no one will visit him.
He told me all this
so you would know.
(Grave Purchase Agreement)
What are you doing?
Turning the tide.
Everyone now thinks
we are back together.
I will drink as a penalty.
The next song is
specially requested by Mr. He
for Ms. Lin beside him.
This is the song
that played in the car
when Mr. He first drove Ms. Lin home.
What first-time home?
What in the car?
How come I don't know about it?
I made it up.
One song costs over 200 yuan.
It is fine. I already paid.
This one is on me.
Sounds good.
(Send to Dai Shan. Confirm.)
I will walk you upstairs.
No need. I can go up myself.
Don't move.
There is something there.
Thank you
for putting on this act with me today.
Maybe I should go up with you.
I have other things to do upstairs.
Head back.
See you tomorrow.
We will talk tomorrow.
Why didn't you come up?
I saw everything from upstairs.
I will walk around downstairs for a bit.
I will come up later.
Why did you come down?
Zhangzhu is there.
Some things are not convenient to say.
So?
How did it feel revisiting the past?
Acting is acting.
You always pick
the best parts to perform.
So, it was good.
When we were good,
we were really good.
When we were not,
it was really bad.
So what we just showed
was the best side of us.
Then, do you think he
was acting or being real?
I don't know.
Do you want him to be acting or real?
Why not
take this chance
to get back together?
Everyone would be happy.
Actually, being fake is not bad.
There is no pressure
or burden.
No need to worry about
fighting and making up again.
It is exhausting.
I have started reading your novels.
While reading,
I even discussed with Er Jiu
what you wrote.
Why are you interested in my novels?
At first, it was confusing.
But as I kept reading, I caught up.
In the comments,
people always compare you with He Han.
I have read He Han's novels.
I think you write better than he does.
You might be the only one
who thinks I write better than He Han.
Did I disturb your writing?
No.
I have not started yet.
Then, you go ahead.
I will leave first.
(Dingqi 2024 Annual Author Night,
Gu Yan)
The trophy is back?
It was delivered.
Then, we should take a photo with it.
You really went all out.
You and Lin Zhanqiao
had flowers
and a candlelight dinner last night.
Want me to get you a megaphone?
So you can announce it
to the whole world.
If I told you I wanted to make it real,
would you believe me?
Do you know who came to see me today?
Mimi.
Even she knows that
you are getting back together
with Lin Zhanqiao.
She thinks
she and I are on the same side,
both exes you let down.
If you had not said it,
I would have forgotten.
We have not officially broken up yet.
Happy breakup.
So easy that I almost
don't want to break up with you.
Would she accept it
if you asked Lin Zhanqiao
to get back together?
It is not my first time.
I have experience.
So you like her more, right?
Of course, she likes me more.
So she carries a heavy burden.
I am more relaxed.
If I make the move
and get rejected, it won't hurt much.
That line might work on others,
but not on me.
If you're so attached,
now that you've
finally gotten back together,
why not fix your issues?
If I were going to change,
I would have long ago.
But honestly,
you have known me for a while.
Do you really think I am
as messy in relationships as people say?
Messy,
but not chaotic.
What I mean is you simply don't know
how to handle relationships properly,
yet you insist on acting like an expert.
Come on,
how many people can do it right?
Okay, one more step.
Okay.
This way.
Grandma,
the drive will take a bit longer today.
You can listen to the radio on the way.
I also brought you
some butterfly pastries.
If you get hungry, you can have some.
Okay.
Alright.
Grandma, step.
Okay, sit tight.
Alright.
Grandma, are you thirsty?
Do you want some water?
No, thanks.
If you need anything later,
just tell me.
Okay.
Grandma, here.
- Okay.
- No rush.
Okay.
We are almost there.
This is fine to eat, right?
Grandma, there is a small river nearby.
Later, you can take a boat ride.
Okay.
You can walk here.
Mom!
That is your daughter?
So beautiful.
Your son-in-law is quite impressive too.
We are here.
Okay.
You are here?
Dad.
Ling Yikai.
Ling Yikai's grandma.
- Hello.
Grandma, this is my dad.
Welcome, Grandma.
(Baixing Restaurant)
Come, please come.
Grandma, let's go inside.
Careful, there are steps.
Okay.
Slowly, lift your foot.
Grandma, have some tea.
Okay.
Ling,
I am really sorry.
For a first meeting between families,
we should have picked
a nicer restaurant.
But as you can see,
I need to keep an eye on the game room
across the street.
So we could only
come to this small place
to have a simple meal together.
Is that alright?
Alright.
Her mom will be done with
mahjong soon and come over.
Let them know they can start cooking.
Okay.
Well,
Ling, do you know how to play mahjong?
I don't, Mr. Zhao.
- Then, you should learn it properly.
- You can start cooking now.
Life is like strong liquor.
Mahjong eases a thousand worries.
But don't worry.
Lanxin will have time
to teach you properly.
Before my daughter could even talk,
she could already play mahjong.
She grew up by the mahjong table.
Eating and sleeping
were all in my game room.
People criticized me
and said that if I did not
raise her properly,
she would turn out badly.
Is that not nonsense?
My daughter is wonderful.
Right?
Now, she is about to get married.
And you're outstanding.
Grandma and I are truly blessed.
Yes.
But I heard from Lanxin
that Ling's
parents are no longer around.
Mr. Zhao,
I have been a burden to my grandson.
Having Grandma, I am already blessed.
Grandma,
I understand what you mean.
Don't worry.
Some families
might care about that,
but ours will not.
I win!
Alright, then.
I will go ahead first.
- Wait, wait.
- Come back later.
You will understand
Lanxin's value more over time.
Leaving other things aside,
birth, aging, illness, and death,
to put it bluntly,
you will not have to worry at all.
Even your own matters,
- I have finished this round.
- she can help you
- take care of them.
- Sorry about that.
They needed one more player,
so I filled in for a few rounds.
That turned into this long.
Ling Yikai and his grandma.
Mrs. Zhao.
- This is my mom.
- Hello.
Let's take a photo together.
They are still waiting for me next door.
Let's go out together.
- Okay.
- Let's take a photo.
- Ask a waiter to help us.
- Waiter.
Come take a photo for us.
Come.
Not playing anymore?
Wait for me a bit.
Zhao.
What?
I don't know what bad luck I had today.
What happened?
I didn't win a single round. Come.
Give me another 500 yuan.
Okay, okay.
After I eat, I will switch with you.
Don't worry.
Hurry up.
Friends?
Grandma, we are all
familiar neighbors here.
Look here.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
- Cheese.
Alright, thank you.
Lanxin.
Grandma.
I want to use the restroom.
- Okay.
- I will take you.
Alright.
Let me see.
There are steps.
Sit, Ling.
Grandma does not know we are divorced?
Divorced?
You did not know?
Lanxin never mentioned it, huh?
Why bring that up?
It was a long time ago.
Let me tell you.
We are divorced.
We both remarried.
That woman just now
is his current wife.
My partner is also playing cards nearby.
Anyway, after going around,
we are all just players
from the game room.
We did think about
splitting up the business.
But it was doing well.
So we discussed it
and decided to continue together,
half and half.
You all get along quite well.
Not bad.
Zhao Lanxin keeps
an eye on things for us.
How the money
is divided is all up to her.
Do you know why?
She is the legal
representative of the game room.
We are all just employees.
She is not someone
who cares about money.
She just likes managing money,
people, and affairs.
Isn't she taking
good care of your grandma now?
Yes.
(Jinbei Law Firm)
Come on in.
Lawyer Bei.
What did you want to see me about?
About the transfer to
the Southwest Branch,
I have decided.
I will go.
Didn't you say before
that you didn't want to leave Shanghai
and didn't want
a long-distance relationship?
Why the sudden change?
Yes.
So I thought
I would propose to Zhou Mei first.
After we get engaged, I will go.
Have you told her?
Not yet.
I was just about to.
What if she does not agree?
That is why I hope
you can come with me to persuade her.
You mean
you want me to go with you?
As my supervisor
and mentor,
you can explain to her the importance
of my going to the Southwest Branch.
You can also tell her
to feel at ease
and wait for me to come back.
I really hope you can help me with this.
Because for me,
this is the best of both worlds.
Please set up a time with her.
Thank you, Lawyer Bei.
I'll leave you to it.
Grandma,
have you withdrawn
your pension this month?
I have.
Zhao helped me withdraw it.
Grandma said she asked you before,
but you kept delaying for days.
Then you should
keep this bank card safe.
Don't leave it lying around,
or you will panic if it gets lost.
Alright?
I will not.
Zhao is keeping it for me.
From now on,
she will withdraw it for me.
I have given her
my medical card and everything.
If I need them, I will go to her.
The bank card,
the medical card,
and what else?
Give them back to me.
They are at my place.
Do you need them now?
Come with me, and I'll get them for you.
This is the passbook.
On this note are
the dates for meter readings
and the payment dates.
You can link the payments to your phone
for automatic payment.
This is for social security.
The regular schedule
and location for medication
are all written here.
Some medicines are not covered, so you
have to buy them at the pharmacy.
I have written where
to buy them as well.
Follow-up visits require
an online appointment in advance
with the time, department,
and doctor selected.
You will also need the senior card,
right?
The community office
- will come by to help clean.
- Okay.
Keep these with you for now.
Do you think
I am after the elderly's money?
How could you care
about this little amount?
I genuinely want to help you.
You already have.
The elderly hesitate to see specialists,
and they are reluctant
to buy imported medicine.
I paid for it myself.
Thank you.
I will give it to you.
You know that is not what I want.
I want you to truly feel I matter.
I do.
How do you want me to show it?
If you really think I matter,
then propose to me.
Marry me.
Is that not too fast?
Too fast.
We have already met
each other's parents.
At least, give me some time to prepare.
Don't make me wait too long.
You really keep
everything in separate bags.
It is easier to manage
and not mix things up.
This is my dad's.
This is my mom's.
There will be one more for you,
Ling Yikai.
Don't push me too hard.
Such a big setup.
You even brought Lawyer Bei.
He is not easy to invite.
I am here as support today.
What is wrong?
It is just a two-year transfer.
I already said I support you.
Say it.
If you don't, I will say it for you?
No, no.
I invited more support.
Let's wait.
Mrs. Bei.
Sorry.
I am late for something this important.
So, where are you now?
Have you started?
You never inform me in advance
when you bring your wife.
Zhang Yousen,
you invited my wife as support,
and you did not tell me?
The more, the merrier.
Yousen is like family to us.
For his future, I have to show support.
Of course, I had to come.
This is a lot.
You are putting me under pressure.
Dating has turned into
something for four people.
We are just here to accompany.
It is mainly up to you.
Right, everyone is here now.
I will say it.
Zhou Mei,
about my transfer to
the Southwest Branch,
Lawyer Bei wants me to go next month.
So I hope you can
wait for me for two years.
I cannot wait.
No matter who asks me,
my answer is the same.
A lot can change in two years.
Two years ago, you did not know me,
and in two years,
I don't know who I will meet.
So I cannot lie to you.
That is one way to look at it,
but Yousen just said it, too.
It is just his wish.
You can also treat it as a wish.
There may be many uncertainties,
but having a shared wish
is better than having none, right?
Yes.
It is not like he will not
come back for two years.
There are holidays
and weekends,
right?
Chengdu, Chongqing, and Guiyang are only
about a three-hour flight from Shanghai.
Nowadays, many people travel back
and forth for work between two cities.
It is very normal.
Besides,
as the saying goes,
when two people love each other,
distance does not matter.
Right?
Zhang Yousen,
you need to be more of a man.
You cannot put all
the pressure on Zhou Mei.
You need to put in the effort
to maintain
your relationship for these two years.
Yes.
I did not ask it well enough.
It is alright.
Let's move past that question.
There is something
more important ahead, right?
Zhou Mei,
before I leave,
I hope you will accept my proposal.
Such a big diamond ring,
where did you get the money to buy it?
Well,
Yousen borrowed money from me.
He insisted on buying you a big one.
He said a small one would not suit you.
So, on behalf of Lawyer Bei,
I advanced his salary to him.
You could say
this is the boss contributing
to an employee's happiness. Right?
Stand up first.
Stand up.
Don't play games,
like you will not get up
unless I say yes.
I really dislike that.
Yousen,
you have made the proposal.
Whether Zhou Mei accepts is up to her.
Come back and sit down.
Come, sit.
I originally wanted
Mrs. Bei and Lawyer Bei
to be witnesses.
If you agreed,
Lawyer Bei would also feel at ease
about my going to Chengdu.
But since you don't agree now,
I am still hesitating
whether to go or not.
Yousen
is a very promising young man.
When I married Lawyer Bei,
he was not even as
outstanding as Yousen.
In two years,
when he returns,
his future will be limitless.
So, Lawyer Bei, what you mean
is that in two years, the one
who changes will not be me,
but Zhang Yousen.
So I should accept this ring now, right?
I think you should accept the ring
to put Yousen at ease.
Once Yousen is at ease,
Lawyer Bei will also be at ease.
Right?
Well...
Yeah,
I feel that if Zhang Yousen
does not go to Chengdu,
it will be troublesome for me.
I would not know who to send.
Someone capable
and willing to go.
So, did Lawyer Bei bring us together
because we are compatible
or for the company's arrangements?
Both, I think.
Where do you think we are compatible?
What if I have other options?
You...
You are publicly a couple,
right?
You look very compatible,
very well-matched.
And you have a promising future.
More importantly,
Zhang Yousen
is wholeheartedly devoted to you.
Yousen,
first,
you did not need to buy
such a big diamond ring.
Whether I accept or not
has nothing to do with its size.
It is just an accessory.
Second,
I will not accept
just because you brought
Lawyer Bei and Mrs. Bei here.
Instead, I feel
you are trying to corner me.
Third,
I am not ready to get married.
It has nothing to do with the ring.
Marriage needs to be taken seriously.
We are only dating.
If we don't have money,
we buy something cheaper.
If we have money later,
we can buy something better.
If I accept
this ring bought with
Lawyer Bei's money,
then whose sincerity
does it represent?
Regarding the company arrangements,
you can continue talking.
I will leave first.
♪If the sky and the sea
turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish fell
in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then we had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain,
that's alright♪
♪If we're buried by passing years,
all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
Hello.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪